{
    "id": "beba746d13fa42378623420cc73a4a21",
    "title": "Gerunds Or Participles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are …………………. too much these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "smoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4195bc9ca27245cfb9e9d5de12bb36ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a …………………… cigarette end in the ashtray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "smoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bc10a888b4b4268b7880d074d400574"
        },
        {
            "question": "Having ………………… for ten hours, I felt great.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sleeping",
                "slept"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43bc42838bfa439ba325c1256d64e456"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not …………………… what to do, I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "known",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "366860e2083240a09d2aca0553c73034"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went ……………………… out of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "running",
                "run"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2a7536e22874007a5505737715b0cec"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… stamps is a hobby of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Collecting",
                "Collected"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f747aeed5c240cabcadc3c22da4a4c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate …………………. suitcases.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "packing",
                "packed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6cc4bcae9f44eaeb55648afc20738a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry at Susie …………………… to lie to her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "trying",
                "tried"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da0939ee96204f919946b64e6ce9d424"
        },
        {
            "question": "The roof was ………………… off in the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blowing",
                "blown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1cba017939f244699679198d75acdbe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested ………………….. a long holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taking",
                "taken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ec5f5d6c3b448a99671b43304e24786"
        }
    ]
}